Devlopers:
-   Siddharth Chikorde (sdchikorde@gmail.com)
-   Vikrant Dhimate (vikrantdhimate@gmail.com)

Hello dear user,

This application is intended to help travellers who are willingful to visit tourist places in India.
  
One may plan his journey to a state in India and visit tourist places in it. Or he may directly search for city in his wish and plan to visit.
  
Traveller will take info about these places, visit them pictorially and will also get directions to reach there from the point he is standing.
  
This application also helps in finding nearby important places like ATM, petrol pump, hotel etc; which makes this app the best companion of traveller.
  
For best performance and experience we suggest you to
    1.Keep internet ON
    2.Keep GPS ON

If you find that we missed some place which you visited and you want to see it in list then please send us an email having 
    1.Information about that place
    2.Couple of pics of tourist spots